<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Tech Tweedie</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/</link><description>Beyond the low code, Tech Tweedie offers comprehensive guides and tutorials on Power Platform, Microsoft technologies, and Hugo. Learn how to build PCF controls, install Hugo on Windows 11, and more. Stay updated with our latest posts and in-depth content.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techtweedie.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🚀 Build Your First Azure DevOps Pipeline for Power Platform (Complete Beginner Tutorial!)</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Have you ever wished you could automatically export your Dataverse solutions, back up your Power Platform work, or finally start using DevOps like the pros? In this step-by-step tutorial, I’ll show you EXACTLY how to build your first Azure DevOps pipeline — even if you’ve never touched DevOps before.</description></item><item><title>D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East – September 2025 Meetup</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250930-d365ppugne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250930-d365ppugne/</guid><description>Join us on September 30 in Newcastle for the D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East meetup. Network with the community and learn from expert sessions on AI grounding and modern Canvas App components.</description></item><item><title>Playwright for Makers – Bringing One-Click UI Tests to Model-Driven Apps &amp; Power Pages</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250910-d365ppugnational/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250910-d365ppugnational/</guid><description>A 40-minute, demo-heavy walkthrough that adds the missing 'test' step to your low-code CI/CD story.</description></item><item><title>Generate Power Platform Solution Documentation with Azure DevOps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</guid><description>Learn how to automatically generate clear, accurate documentation for your Power Platform solutions using the Power Platform Documentation Extension for Azure DevOps.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic Episode 7: Automatically Tag DevOps Tickets by Email</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250720-power-platform-clinic-episode-seven/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250720-power-platform-clinic-episode-seven/</guid><description>In this session of the Power Platform Clinic, we walk through a brilliant way to automatically post email content to Azure DevOps work items using Power Automate and plus addressing. If you're working with teams outside your scrum or chasing up suppliers, this trick can keep your board updated with zero manual effort.</description></item><item><title>Running ADVANCED Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Run Playwright tests in Azure DevOps for your Power Platform apps with dynamic user role assignment, business unit switching, and detailed test results.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic - Episode 6: Certs, Consultancy, and Career Conversations</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250713-power-platform-clinic-episode-six/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250713-power-platform-clinic-episode-six/</guid><description>In Episode 6 of the Power Platform Clinic, Duncan and Ian dive into Microsoft certifications, consultancy life, and how to build a well-rounded career in the Power Platform space. They tackle real questions from the community and share their experiences from both ends of the consultant spectrum.</description></item><item><title>Running Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Learn how to run Playwright tests on your Power Platform model-driven apps using a free Azure DevOps extension. This tutorial walks you through installing the extension, creating a pipeline, and viewing your results with HTML reports and trace analysis.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 5: Converting Forms with Images to PDF</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250625-power-platform-clinic-episode-five/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250625-power-platform-clinic-episode-five/</guid><description>In Episode 5 of the Power Platform Clinic, Duncan and Ian walk through converting a Microsoft Form—complete with text and image uploads—into a structured PDF using Power Automate. This proof of concept demonstrates data handling, file encoding, dynamic HTML generation, and emailing the final document.</description></item><item><title>Walkthrough Customising Entra External ID for Power Pages</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</guid><description>In this blog post, we walk through the process of customising the login experience for Power Pages using Entra External ID. We’ll show how to apply branding to the sign-in screen to make it look and feel like your organisation, creating a seamless experience for external users.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 4: Power Pages Authentication Options and Developer Accounts</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250603-power-platform-clinic-episode-four/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250603-power-platform-clinic-episode-four/</guid><description>In Episode 2 of Power Platform Clinic, Ian Tweedy and Duncan Boyne explore the different authentication options for Power Pages and guide you through how to set up your own developer account for Power Platform experimentation and learning.</description></item><item><title>D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East – June 2025 Meetup</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250626-d365ppugne/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250626-d365ppugne/</guid><description>Join us on June 26 in Newcastle for the D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East meetup. Network with the community and learn from expert sessions on AI grounding and modern Canvas App components.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 3: Calling a Dad Joke API and Custom Visuals in Power BI Clinic</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250526-power-platform-clinic-episode-three/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250526-power-platform-clinic-episode-three/</guid><description>In this Power Platform Clinic session, we showed how to call an external API from Power Automate using icanhazdadjoke.com, and Duncan demonstrated how to connect and configure Power BI custom visuals with your data.</description></item><item><title>Walk through Power Pages with Entra External ID</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250524-power-pages-with-entra-external-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250524-power-pages-with-entra-external-id/</guid><description>In this walkthrough, we explore how to configure and integrate Entra External ID with Power Pages to streamline authentication for external users. Whether you’re working with partners, customers, or a public-facing site, this guide shows you how to enable secure, Entra ID-based access with minimal fuss.</description></item><item><title>At the Norfolk Power Platform User Group: Enabling Low-Code Developers to Create Custom Client Reports with a Helping Hand from Azure – Norfolk Power Platform User Group</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250522-nppug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250522-nppug/</guid><description>In this session at the Norfolk Power Platform User Group, I shared how low-code developers can create secure, custom client reports using Power Automate and Azure. Learn about reverse proxy functions, integrating Azure Functions with Power Automate, and deploying the solution in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 2</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250520-power-platform-clinic-episode-two/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250520-power-platform-clinic-episode-two/</guid><description>In this episode of the Power Platform Clinic, Duncan and Ian discuss validating email domains using Power Automate, and Duncan shows how to create a Power BI app to collate reports for users.</description></item><item><title>Show and Hide Tabs Based on Status Reason in Model Driven Apps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250412-show-hide-status-reason/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250412-show-hide-status-reason/</guid><description>In this post, I share a simple JavaScript snippet you can use in Model-Driven Apps to show or hide tabs based on the Status Reason of a record. It’s clean, easy to implement, and great for improving the user experience.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic Episode 1</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250412-power-platform-clinic-episode-one/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250412-power-platform-clinic-episode-one/</guid><description>Welcome to the very first episode of Power Platform Clinic! In this session, Duncan and Ian tackle two real-world Power Platform questions: showing/hiding tabs dynamically in model-driven apps and understanding calculated columns vs measures in Power BI.</description></item><item><title>D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East – March 2025 Meetup</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250327-d365ppugne/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250327-d365ppugne/</guid><description>Catch up on our March 2025 meetup in Newcastle for the D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East. Learn from expert sessions on overcoming Business Rule limitations with JavaScript and adapting Power Pages to GDS standards.</description></item><item><title>At the Scottish Power Platform User Group: Enabling Low-Code Developers to Create Custom Client Reports with a Helping Hand from Azure – Scottish Power Platform User Group</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250325-sppug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250325-sppug/</guid><description>In this session at the Scottish Power Platform User Group, I shared how low-code developers can create secure, custom client reports using Power Automate and Azure. Learn about reverse proxy functions, integrating Azure Functions with Power Automate, and deploying the solution in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>Set folder permissions in SharePoint with Power Automate Flow</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:06:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</guid><description>Discover how to set item or folder permissions in SharePoint using Power Automate Flow with a custom connector and service principal in this comprehensive step-by-step guide.</description></item><item><title>Send Emails from Flow without a Service Account</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250210-send-emails-from-flow-without-a-service-account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250210-send-emails-from-flow-without-a-service-account/</guid><description>Learn how to send emails from Power Automate without a service account! 🚀 This step-by-step guide walks you through setting up an App Registration, securing permissions in Exchange Online, and using a custom connector—no password resets or login issues. Perfect for secure, scalable email automation in Microsoft 365! 🔗 #PowerAutomate #Microsoft365 #Automation</description></item><item><title>At Birmingham Power Platform User Group: Enabling Low-Code Developers to Create Custom Client Reports with a Helping Hand from Azure – Norfolk Power Platform User Group</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250130-bppug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250130-bppug/</guid><description>In this session at the Norfolk Power Platform User Group, I shared how low-code developers can create secure, custom client reports using Power Automate and Azure. Learn about reverse proxy functions, integrating Azure Functions with Power Automate, and deploying the solution in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>At Learner to Leader: Avoid Costly Mistakes: Backing Up Your Power Platform Development Environment</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241214-backing-up-your-development-environment-avoiding-costly-mistakes-in-low-code-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241214-backing-up-your-development-environment-avoiding-costly-mistakes-in-low-code-development/</guid><description>In this session with the Power Platform Learner to Leader community, I shared how to avoid common mistakes and data loss by backing up your Power Platform development environment using Azure DevOps pipelines. Here's a step-by-step guide you can follow.</description></item><item><title>Enabling Low-Code Developers to Create Custom Client Reports with a Helping Hand from Azure – Low Code No Code Conference</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241109-lcnc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241109-lcnc/</guid><description>In this session at the Low Code No Code Microsoft Power Platform Conference 2024, I will share how low-code developers can create secure, custom client reports using Power Automate and Azure. Learn about reverse proxy functions, integrating Azure Functions with Power Automate, and deploying the solution in your own environment.</description></item><item><title>Effortlessly Move Dataverse for Teams Solutions</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/effortlessly-move-dataverse-for-teams-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/effortlessly-move-dataverse-for-teams-solutions/</guid><description>Learn how to easily move Dataverse for Teams solutions between environments using a simple PowerShell script. This step-by-step guide walks you through the entire process—no need for Azure DevOps—helping you manage solution exports, imports, and version tracking with Git. Perfect for both beginners and seasoned developers looking for a streamlined approach to solution management.</description></item><item><title>At the Virtual Power Platform User Group Presenting - Avoid Costly Mistakes: Backing Up Your Power Platform Development Environment</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241003-vd365ppug/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/241003-vd365ppug/</guid><description>In this session with the Power Platform Learner to Leader community, I shared how to avoid common mistakes and data loss by backing up your Power Platform development environment using Azure DevOps pipelines. Here's a step-by-step guide you can follow.</description></item><item><title>Calculate Working Day</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/240924-calculate-working-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/240924-calculate-working-day/</guid><description>Calculating working days in Power Automate can be challenging due to the various factors like weekends, holidays, and custom schedules. To help simplify this process, I’ve developed a tool designed to handle multiple working day scenarios with ease. This post walks you through the setup and usage of the tool, complete with step-by-step instructions.</description></item><item><title>Backup Dataverse Development Environment</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 07:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</guid><description>Ever wondered what would happen if you lost your development environment? How do you feel about having to do all of that work again? What about if you spot a problem days later? Can you remember the value you changed three days ago in that flow? Have you ever seen someone delete the website record by mistake.</description></item><item><title>Securing Power Automate for Production</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/securing-power-automate-for-production/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/securing-power-automate-for-production/</guid><description>Power Automate is a wonderful tool, but there is a world of difference between building something for personal productivity and utilising this amazing low-code tool for production, where an important business application will rely on it.</description></item><item><title>Command Bar to Call Custom Page in Model Driven App</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/command-bar-to-call-custom-page/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 19:32:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/command-bar-to-call-custom-page/</guid><description>Recently I was asked if it was possible to place a message at the top of every form, and every view across an entire Model Driven App. This message would then open up a Custom Page that would display more detail. In this Blog post I go into detail in to how this can be achieved.</description></item><item><title>Build a Basic PCF Field Control</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/build-a-basic-pcf-field-control/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 19:32:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/build-a-basic-pcf-field-control/</guid><description>Want to get started using the Power Apps Component Framework (PCF), would you like to start building controls. In this blog post we are going to step through the process to building your first component.</description></item><item><title>How to Install Hugo on Windows 11</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/how-to-install-hugo-on-windows-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:32:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/how-to-install-hugo-on-windows-11/</guid><description>In this tutorial, we’ll dive into the world of Hugo, a powerful and lightning-fast static site generator. Whether you’re a developer, blogger, or content creator, Hugo can simplify your workflow and help you build efficient, static websites. By the end of this tutorial, you’ll be equipped to create stunning static websites using Hugo. Let’s get started!</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Developer Tools Install Script</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/power-platform-developer-tools-install-script/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:32:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/power-platform-developer-tools-install-script/</guid><description>Frequently moving between desktop builds, want to be able to get up and running quickly,  I’ve found it incredibly useful to have my own build script that covers 80% of the tools I am likely to need. It's essential tools ready to go saves a lot of time and hassle, that’s why I created a PowerShell script to automate the installation of the developer tools I often use when working on the Power Platform.</description></item><item><title>Variables in PowerFX Command Buttons</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/variables-in-powerfx-command-buttons/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/variables-in-powerfx-command-buttons/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered if you can use Environment Variables in a PowerFX button, how to create a custom email link button in the command bar of your Power Apps model-driven application using environment variables and Power FX? Luckily, Power Apps has recently made it possible to achieve this. With the help of Power FX, which is the same language used in canvas app development, anyone can efficiently customise their app’s command bar without needing prior knowledge of JavaScript or the Ribbon Workbench.</description></item><item><title>Clone with PowerFX Command button</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/clone-with-powerfx-command-button/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/clone-with-powerfx-command-button/</guid><description>Cloning multiple records within a data view in a Model-Driven App is a common request from end users. It helps them quickly fill out data fields in situations where only a few values differ between records.</description></item><item><title>Streamlining Webhook Testing</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/steamlining-webhook-testing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/steamlining-webhook-testing/</guid><description>I often find myself undertaking some form of prototyping or investigation. For instance lets say I am publishing an end point for a client to connect to via a HTTP call, often also referred to as a web hook.</description></item><item><title>Create a Solution Configuration File</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/choose-what-dataverse-search-indexes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/choose-what-dataverse-search-indexes/</guid><description>Want to deploy your Power Apps Solution files quickly via Pipelines? Not sure how to set your environment variable or connection references.  This blog post will explain how we solved this problem using a Solution Configuration File. </description></item><item><title>Bias of Maslow’s Hammer</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/bias-of-maslows-hammer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/bias-of-maslows-hammer/</guid><description>In the vast and evolving landscape of software development, the principles guiding our choices often transcend the technical. One psychological concept, Maslow’s Hammer, poignantly captures a cognitive bias that impacts much more than our personal lives—it resonates deeply within the realm of software architecture.</description></item><item><title>Too Many Redirects on WordPress</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/too-many-redirects-on-wordpress/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/too-many-redirects-on-wordpress/</guid><description>I recently set up a new WordPress website for a friend. It was late one evening, and I was in a bit of a rush; as with many people online, I chose to use Cloudflare to protect the website.</description></item><item><title>Thinking Environment Meetings</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/thinking-environment-meetings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/thinking-environment-meetings/</guid><description>In today’s remote work environment, the significance of effective team meetings cannot be overstated. These gatherings are pivotal for aligning goals, addressing challenges, and fostering team cohesion.</description></item><item><title>Azure Function with Azure B2C</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/azure-function-with-azure-b2c/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/azure-function-with-azure-b2c/</guid><description>Azure functions are a very handy way of getting something small done very quickly. Often these have to be secured and sometimes with an identity provider that is not stright out of the box.</description></item><item><title>Postman to Azure Table Storage</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/postman-to-azure-table-storage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/postman-to-azure-table-storage/</guid><description>This post is an example of how I posted data to Azure Table storage from Postman.</description></item><item><title>Azure B2C oAuth on Postman</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/azureb2c-oauth-in-postman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/azureb2c-oauth-in-postman/</guid><description>I had a problem where I needed to get my JWT token from Azure B2C OAuth 2.0 in order to troubleshoot an issue I was having in getting OAuth 2.0 working.</description></item><item><title>PFX certificate for FREE for Power Pages</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/pfx-certificate-for-free-for-power-pages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/pfx-certificate-for-free-for-power-pages/</guid><description>Do you want to deploy Power Pages on a custom domain securely without the need to buy a custom certificate? In this blog post, I’m going to show you how to do this quickly and easily acquire a PFX certificate that you can then use to deploy to Power Pages. </description></item><item><title>Query Parameters on HTTP Trigger</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/query-parameters-on-http-trigger/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/query-parameters-on-http-trigger/</guid><description>When your flow is triggered via an HTTP request, it might need to behave differently based on the values passed through query parameters. For instance, you may want your flow to process data differently depending on a user ID or a specific action indicated in the URL.</description></item></channel></rss>