<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Trubbleshooting - Category - Tech Tweedie</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/trubbleshooting/</link>
        <description>Trubbleshooting - Category - Tech Tweedie</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:00:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/trubbleshooting/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Too Many Redirects on WordPress</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/too-many-redirects-on-wordpress/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/too-many-redirects-on-wordpress/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction I recently set up a new WordPress website for a friend. It was late one evening, and I was in a bit of a rush; as with many people online, I chose to use Cloudflare to protect the website.
However, problems arose after setting up the WordPress website when I configured the SSL/TLS side of things.
I switched on Cloudflare’s proxy as normal.
So far so good.
Then I continued to edit the site before handing it over to my friend; however, I noticed I was getting load errors.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Postman to Azure Table Storage</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/postman-to-azure-table-storage/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 19:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/postman-to-azure-table-storage/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This post is an example of how I posted data to Azure Table storage from Postman.
Prerequisite You have access to Postman You have an Azure Storage account Steps Go to your Storage Account Click on Tables, and then click on Add table Add table to Azure Storage Account
You should now have a table, in my example these are called test and test2.
Next, generate a shared access signature (SAS), which is a URI that grants restricted access.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Azure B2C oAuth on Postman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/azureb2c-oauth-in-postman/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 19:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/azureb2c-oauth-in-postman/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I had a problem where I needed to get my JWT token from Azure B2C OAuth 2.0 in order to troubleshoot an issue I was having in getting OAuth 2.0 working.
Situation I needed to get the JWT token using Postman, decrypt it, and then provide it for troubleshooting the issue.
How did I do that Get postman Create a new request, as far as I am aware it makes no difference what type of request you use so in this example, I will use a GET request.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
