<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Power BI - Tag - Tech Tweedie</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/power-bi/</link>
        <description>Power BI - Tag - Tech Tweedie</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/power-bi/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 3: Calling a Dad Joke API and Custom Visuals in Power BI Clinic</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/250526-power-platform-clinic-episode-three/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/250526-power-platform-clinic-episode-three/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome back to the Power Platform Clinic, your weekly check-in for diagnosing everyday Power Platform challenges — and fixing them without the consulting invoice.
Whether you&rsquo;re a maker, a consultant, or someone who just typed &ldquo;Power Automate funny API&rdquo; into Google — you’re in the right place.
In this week’s episode (Episode 3!), co-hosted by myself (Tech Tweedie) and Duncan (Power BI Kinda Guy), we tackled two questions you’ve either already asked — or definitely will soon.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 2</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/250520-power-platform-clinic-episode-two/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/250520-power-platform-clinic-episode-two/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome to Episode 2 of the Power Platform Clinic with Duncan and Ian!
In this episode:
✅ Validating Email Domains with Power Automate Ian shares a powerful, free way to validate email domains using Power Automate, showing:
Why validating the entire email address is tricky without sending a link How to split out the domain using the split function Using the CheckDomain connector to confirm whether a domain exists and can receive emails How this approach avoids the costs of third-party services and can be used with data from anywhere: Dataverse, Excel, or SharePoint Ian walks through building the flow step by step, demonstrating how it splits the email, checks the domain, and writes the result back to a field in Dataverse to clean up data input.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Power Platform Clinic Episode 1</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/250412-power-platform-clinic-episode-one/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/250412-power-platform-clinic-episode-one/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the very first episode of Power Platform Clinic with Duncan and Ian.
In this episode:
✅ Topic 1 – Show/Hide Tabs Dynamically in Model Driven Apps Ian walks through how to show or hide a whole tab in a model-driven app based on the value of a field, such as Status Reason. The demo covers:
Why you might want to hide/show tabs A full explanation of the JavaScript snippet used How to upload and register the script in your form libraries Gotchas to watch out for (like needing to register the event handler onload and onchange) Testing the functionality and reviewing console logs to understand what&rsquo;s happening under the hood 👉 This approach is especially useful when you only want tabs visible at specific record statuses instead of toggling individual fields.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
