<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Backup - Tag - Tech Tweedie</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/backup/</link>
        <description>Backup - Tag - Tech Tweedie</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:00:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/backup/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Avoid Costly Mistakes: Backing Up Your Power Platform Development Environment</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/241214-backing-up-your-development-environment-avoiding-costly-mistakes-in-low-code-development/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 06:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/241214-backing-up-your-development-environment-avoiding-costly-mistakes-in-low-code-development/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-would-happen-if-you-lost-your-dev-environment">What Would Happen If You Lost Your Dev Environment?</h2>
<p>Ever wondered what would happen if someone accidentally deleted your development site or overwrote a key flow? Rebuilding from memory isn&rsquo;t just frustrating — it’s costly.</p>
<p>This post walks through the process I demonstrated during my session with the <strong>Power Platform Learner to Leader</strong> community, showing how to <strong>automatically back up</strong> your environment using <strong>Azure DevOps</strong>, without requiring advanced YAML knowledge.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Backup Dataverse Development Environment</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 07:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2>
<p>Ever wondered what would happen if you lost your development environment? How do you feel about having to do all of that work again? What about if you spot a problem days later? Can you remember the value you changed three days ago in that flow? Have you ever seen someone delete the website record by mistake.</p>
<p>These are all situations I have been in over the last few years, and having a Pipeline in place to ensure backup of your hard work is extremely important. That historical record can save you many hours.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
