<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Power Automate - Category - Tech Tweedie</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/power-automate/</link>
        <description>Power Automate - Category - Tech Tweedie</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:06:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/power-automate/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Set folder permissions in SharePoint with Power Automate Flow</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:06:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Want to grand and remove item or folder permissions in SharePoint using Power Automate with a Service Principle but can&rsquo;t do it? Not able to do it with the out of the box SharePoint Connector?
Tired of dealing with Conditional Access Policies, password expirations, and frequent logins?
Good news! In this guide, I&rsquo;ll show you how to set these using an App Registration. No service accounts, no password headaches. I&rsquo;ll also share a Custom Connector to make it even easier, plus step-by-step instructions to:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Send Emails from Flow without a Service Account</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/send-emails-from-flow-without-a-service-account/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 09:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/send-emails-from-flow-without-a-service-account/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Want to send emails from Power Automate but can&rsquo;t or don&rsquo;t want to use a service account? Tired of dealing with Conditional Access Policies, password expirations, and frequent logins? Do you want a simple, secure, and scalable way to send emails without constantly re-confirming security information?
Good news! In this guide, I&rsquo;ll show you how to send emails directly from Microsoft Exchange using only an App Registration. No service accounts, no password headaches.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Query Parameters on HTTP Trigger</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/query-parameters-on-http-trigger/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/query-parameters-on-http-trigger/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Working with Power Automate, especially with HTTP triggers, can unlock a lot of potential in automating tasks and workflows. A common requirement is to use query parameters from the trigger URL within your flow. I’ve found a straightforward method to do this and thought it might be helpful to share.
When your flow is triggered via an HTTP request, it might need to behave differently based on the values passed through query parameters.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
