<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>How To - Category - Tech Tweedie</title>
        <link>http://localhost:53760/categories/how-to/</link>
        <description>How To - Category - Tech Tweedie</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:53760/categories/how-to/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Generate Power Platform Solution Documentation with Azure DevOps</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Your First Azure DevOps Pipeline for Power Platform – A Complete Beginner’s Guide Have you ever wondered how to set up Azure DevOps pipelines for the Power Platform?
Ever wished you could export your solutions safely, run tests, add security checks, generate documentation, or deploy across tenants with confidence?
All of this becomes simple once you introduce Azure DevOps into your Power Platform ALM story — and in this guide (based on my YouTube walkthrough), I’ll show you exactly how to build your first Azure DevOps pipeline.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Generate Power Platform Solution Documentation with Azure DevOps</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Instantly Document Your Power Platform Solutions with Azure DevOps Are you tired of manually documenting your Power Platform solutions? Struggling to keep your tables, relationships, option sets, and workflows up to date for your team or clients? The Power Platform Documentation Extension for Azure DevOps is designed to solve these problems—automatically. This tool helps you generate clear, accurate, and SEO-friendly Markdown documentation for your wikis and repositories, saving you hours and improving collaboration.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Running ADVANCED Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[🧪 Playwright + Power Platform + DevOps Pipelines? Yes please! Just dropped a new video where I walk through the latest update to my Playwright for Power Platform DevOps Extension. This time, we’re not just running tests — we’re dynamically assigning roles, business units, and teams to a test user before your Playwright test runs, and then removing them right after. Clean, controlled, reusable testing every time ✅
🎯 What&rsquo;s new in this release?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Running Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Are you looking to easily run Playwright tests for your Power Platform apps within an Azure DevOps pipeline? In this tutorial, I show you how to use my Playwright for Power Platform DevOps extension to run tests against your model-driven app, capture reports, and publish results.
Below is the embedded video:
What you will learn How to install the Playwright for Power Platform DevOps extension How to write a Playwright test that creates a Contact record using fake data How to set up your Azure DevOps pipeline to run these tests, archive reports, and publish results Code Snippet – Playwright Test Here is the test script used in the video to add a contact with fake data:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Walkthrough Customising Entra External ID for Power Pages</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Walkthrough Customising Entra External ID for Power Pages Introduction Are you using Entra External ID with Power Pages and want to customise the login experience? This guide walks through exactly that — applying your own branding, images, colours, and layout to the Entra login screen for external users.
This is especially useful for creating a polished, consistent experience when your users are accessing Power Pages from outside your organisation.
If you’re new to setting up Entra External ID for Power Pages, I’ve also got a full video walkthrough on how to configure that — I’ll link it below.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Walk through Power Pages with Entra External ID</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250524-power-pages-with-entra-external-id/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 06:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250524-power-pages-with-entra-external-id/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Need to enable Entra External ID sign-in for your Power Pages site? Whether you&rsquo;re looking to support customer access or enable collaboration with external users, the combination of Power Pages and Entra ID is a powerful way to ensure secure, identity-driven access to your platform.
In this walkthrough video, I demonstrate how to integrate Entra External ID with a Power Pages site, covering:
Setting up Entra External ID Configuring identity providers Connecting the authentication flow with your Power Pages site Testing the login experience from an external user’s perspective Why Use Entra External ID with Power Pages?]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Set folder permissions in SharePoint with Power Automate Flow</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:06:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/250217-set-folder-permissions-in-sharepoint-with-power-automate-flow/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Want to grand and remove item or folder permissions in SharePoint using Power Automate with a Service Principle but can&rsquo;t do it? Not able to do it with the out of the box SharePoint Connector?
Tired of dealing with Conditional Access Policies, password expirations, and frequent logins?
Good news! In this guide, I&rsquo;ll show you how to set these using an App Registration. No service accounts, no password headaches. I&rsquo;ll also share a Custom Connector to make it even easier, plus step-by-step instructions to:]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Backup Dataverse Development Environment</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 07:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/backup-dataverse-development-environment/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Ever wondered what would happen if you lost your development environment? How do you feel about having to do all of that work again? What about if you spot a problem days later? Can you remember the value you changed three days ago in that flow? Have you ever seen someone delete the website record by mistake.
These are all situations I have been in over the last few years, and having a Pipeline in place to ensure backup of your hard work is extremely important.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Azure Function with Azure B2C</title>
    <link>http://localhost:53760/posts/azure-function-with-azure-b2c/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 19:00:00 &#43;0100</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:53760/posts/azure-function-with-azure-b2c/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Azure functions are a very handy way of getting something small done very quickly. Often these have to be secured and sometimes with an identity provider that is not stright out of the box.
Today I am going to take you through the steps I took to secure an azure function using Azure B2C.
Step 1 – Create app in Azure B2C PREREQUISITE Azure Function The Azure Function URL Azure B2C Tenant configured with user flows STEP 1 To start with register an application in Azure B2C.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
