<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Tech Tweedie</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Tech Tweedie</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>🚀 Build Your First Azure DevOps Pipeline for Power Platform (Complete Beginner Tutorial!)</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/251118-your-first-azure-devops-pipeline-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Have you ever wished you could automatically export your Dataverse solutions, back up your Power Platform work, or finally start using DevOps like the pros? In this step-by-step tutorial, I’ll show you EXACTLY how to build your first Azure DevOps pipeline — even if you’ve never touched DevOps before.</description></item><item><title>D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East – September 2025 Meetup</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250930-d365ppugne/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250930-d365ppugne/</guid><description>Join us on September 30 in Newcastle for the D365 &amp; Power Platform UG North East meetup. Network with the community and learn from expert sessions on AI grounding and modern Canvas App components.</description></item><item><title>Playwright for Makers – Bringing One-Click UI Tests to Model-Driven Apps &amp; Power Pages</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250910-d365ppugnational/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250910-d365ppugnational/</guid><description>A 40-minute, demo-heavy walkthrough that adds the missing 'test' step to your low-code CI/CD story.</description></item><item><title>Generate Power Platform Solution Documentation with Azure DevOps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250904-power-platform-documentation-extension/</guid><description>Learn how to automatically generate clear, accurate documentation for your Power Platform solutions using the Power Platform Documentation Extension for Azure DevOps.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic Episode 7: Automatically Tag DevOps Tickets by Email</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250720-power-platform-clinic-episode-seven/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250720-power-platform-clinic-episode-seven/</guid><description>In this session of the Power Platform Clinic, we walk through a brilliant way to automatically post email content to Azure DevOps work items using Power Automate and plus addressing. If you're working with teams outside your scrum or chasing up suppliers, this trick can keep your board updated with zero manual effort.</description></item><item><title>Running ADVANCED Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250715-running-advanced-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Run Playwright tests in Azure DevOps for your Power Platform apps with dynamic user role assignment, business unit switching, and detailed test results.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic - Episode 6: Certs, Consultancy, and Career Conversations</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250713-power-platform-clinic-episode-six/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250713-power-platform-clinic-episode-six/</guid><description>In Episode 6 of the Power Platform Clinic, Duncan and Ian dive into Microsoft certifications, consultancy life, and how to build a well-rounded career in the Power Platform space. They tackle real questions from the community and share their experiences from both ends of the consultant spectrum.</description></item><item><title>Running Playwright Tests in Azure DevOps for Power Platform Apps</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250702-running-playwright-tests-in-azure-devops-for-power-platform/</guid><description>Learn how to run Playwright tests on your Power Platform model-driven apps using a free Azure DevOps extension. This tutorial walks you through installing the extension, creating a pipeline, and viewing your results with HTML reports and trace analysis.</description></item><item><title>Power Platform Clinic – Episode 5: Converting Forms with Images to PDF</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250625-power-platform-clinic-episode-five/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250625-power-platform-clinic-episode-five/</guid><description>In Episode 5 of the Power Platform Clinic, Duncan and Ian walk through converting a Microsoft Form—complete with text and image uploads—into a structured PDF using Power Automate. This proof of concept demonstrates data handling, file encoding, dynamic HTML generation, and emailing the final document.</description></item><item><title>Walkthrough Customising Entra External ID for Power Pages</title><link>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://techtweedie.github.io/posts/250624-power-pages-customise-entra-external-id/</guid><description>In this blog post, we walk through the process of customising the login experience for Power Pages using Entra External ID. We’ll show how to apply branding to the sign-in screen to make it look and feel like your organisation, creating a seamless experience for external users.</description></item></channel></rss>